你们觉得 开记者招待会有多难
Hey,how hard do you guys think it would be to throw a press conference?
- 什么主题 - 有道理
- About what? - Yeah,you're right.
收到Shershow的邮件 他要结婚了
I just got an e-mail from shershow. He's getting married.
- 谁会嫁给Shershow - 疯了
- Who would marry shershow? - Oh,this is crazy.
"尽管我和Melinda相识仅仅两个月"
"though melinda and I met but two short months ago,
"但我俩已如纳威人的头发般不可分离"
"our bond is an inseparable as the na'vi people's hair penetration"?
纳威人:阿凡达中 潘多拉星球的生物
真是个傻蛋
The guy's such an idiot.
- Shershow要结婚了 - 就在这周六 我们的结婚纪念日
- Shershow's getting married. - This saturday,on our anniversary.
不是 我们结婚纪念日是...本周六唉
No,our anniversary is... This saturday!
在我们纪念日结婚 真是他会干的事
This is classic shershow to get married on our day.
所有计划都得改变了
You're gonna have to change all the plans you made.
讨厌 我都安排得那么好了
Damn it! They were such good plans,too.
人家计划了...
It's... All the...
巧克力和...旅行
The chocolate and... Trips and...
巧克力旅行
Chocolate trips?
蜡烛...丝绸床单...精油
Candles... Silk sheets and... oil.
- 得加上精油 - 好
- Gotta have oil. - Okay.
说真的 Shershow居然比我先结婚
Seriously,guys. I can't believe shershow is getting married before me.
他是我的备胎
He was my safety.
我们约好 若40岁还是单身
I mean,we made a pact if we didn't find anyone by 40,
我们就结婚
then we'd just marry each other.
你想嫁给Shershow吗
You'd actually marry shershow?
这就像我奶奶包里的枪
It's kinda like the gun in my grandma's purse.
她希望用不到它 但放着有安全感
She hopes she doesn't have to use it, but she likes knowing it's there.
我以为Shershow会是万年光棍的
I mean,I thought shershow was the safest safety possible.
他是疯子 我们去保释了他几次
The guy's a maniac. How many times have we bailed him out?
- 一次从牢里 还有一次从船上 - 可不嘛
- Once out of jail and once out of an actual boat. - Oh,right.
还记得那年夏天 他跟咱住一块儿吗
Remember that summer he stayed with us?
我录的公牛队比赛哪去了
Where's my bulls game?
咋存了15个小时的Maury Povich秀
And why do we have 15 hours of maury povich?
我加入了Povich粉丝后援会
Because I'm in a fantasy povich league.
借过 让我挤过去
Excuse me. Let me just nestle through here.
老天
Oh,golly.
他肚脐眼有够深的
Such a deep belly button.
哪有那次惨 他烧了我的公寓唉
It wasn't as bad as the time he made smoothies at my apartment.
Shershow有毛病
Shershow has issues.
你穿着睡衣来酒吧 还有脸说别人
Says the guy who wears the pajama top to the bar.
- 真的 - 其实
- It's true. - You know what?
鉴于Shershow现在重新做人了
Actually,now that shershow's getting his life together,
你就成了新一代的Shershow
that kinda makes you the new shershow,man.
- 对啊 - 没错唉
- yes! - Yes,you are.
这里来点啤酒
Can I get a beer,please?
你的生活真是一团糟
Your life is in shambles.
让你们失望了
Well,the joke is on all of you,
人家下面穿的是泳裤
because I am wearing my bathing suit bottoms.
Brad 我的啤酒由你付钱
Brad,pay for my beer.
他穿了泳裤
oh,He has bathing suit bottoms on!
- 要命了 - 抗不牢了
- He is gonna die soon. - I can't! I can't.
- Shershow! - Shershow!
<font color=#38B0DE> -=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 呸呸 撒酷啦 大金 Achilles之踵 阿吐 校对: 奔波王 时间轴: 卡灰 双语合成兼压制：神秘人士</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>幸福终点站 第1季 第12集
<font color=#38B0DE>happy.endings S01E12</font>
昨晚约会好玩吗
So,al,did you have fun on your date last night?
没到那一步
Uh,wouldn't go that far.
- 今晚很开心 - 我也是
- I had a great time. - Me,too.
我要戴套套吗
So... Should I get a condom?
什么 不用
What? No.
太好了 我也不喜欢戴套
Sweet! I hate condoms,too.
- 怎么这样 - 男人都这样
- Who does that? - They all do that.
我都忘了约会多可怕了 赶紧让我遇到个正常男人吧
I forgot how much dating sucks, and I just wish I could find a normal guy,
因为人家很久没有平躺运动了
'cause to be honest,it's been a while since I did the old lay down,move around.
- 什么意思 - 就是"闹区游走"啦
- I'm sorry. What was that? - You know,the old downtown parade.
- 还是没懂 - 听不懂
- I don't follow. - Still not getting it.
我是说好久没做爱啦
Sex! I'm talking about sex!
- 明白了 平躺... - 对对对
The lay down. Okay,and then you... Yeah,yeah,yeah.
大家好
Hi,guys.
给你带来了点三明治
Thought I'd bring you some... Sandwiches.
- 你们在干嘛呢 - 女生之间聊聊天
- What is going on here? - Just some girl talk.
等等 你们在聊Alex和别的男人吗
Wait. You guys are talking about alex and a dude,right?
没有
No.
没关系 我们是朋友
Guys,I'm cool. I mean,we are friends.
聊这类事情完全没问题
We gotta be open about this kind of stuff.
你说得对 我和Connor出去约会
You're right. All right,so basically I go on a date with connor.
接吻后 他就掏出了...
One kiss,and he's pulling out -
够了 这是个好的开始
okay,that's a good start.
咱周六不在家 那要在今天交换礼物吗
So should we exchange anniversary gifts today
since we won't be here on saturday?
不 再等5至8个工作日吧
No,let's wait... Five to eight more business days.
提前一天不行吗
Couldn't have overnighted it?
- 你们好 - 你们在干嘛呢
- Oh,hey,guys. - What are you guys doing here?
Shershow跟修有线电视的打了一架
Shershow over here got in a fight with our cable guy.
很黄很暴力 所以俺们电视就啥节目都没了
It was raining shin kicks. Needless to say,no más espn deportes.
你好好想想
Well,riddle me this.
如果我是Shershow 那他怎么让我给他主持婚礼呢
If I'm so shershow,how come the real shershow just asked me
to officiate his wedding?
看吧 别扯了
Boom. Stink it.
请原谅 我得开始申请我的牧师执照了
Now if you'll excuse me,I have to apply for my minister's license.
是更新你的牧师执照吧 你还主持了我们的婚礼呢
You mean renew your license,'cause you officiated our wedding.
你给我们主持婚礼时 是有执照的吧
You did have your license when you married us,right?
你在说什么 我没有啊
Funny story. No?
她的脸咋了
What's happening with her face?
她正在做"漂亮地回忆" 让她回忆完吧
Ah,she's "beautiful mind-ing" it. Just gotta let it play itself out.
Brad 你知道这意味着什么吗
Brad! You know what this means,right?
我们可以再来一次蜜月嘿咻
We get to have honeymoon sex again,
我可以再一次把那啥...放进你那啥...
and I get to put my c... Ar keys in your a... Ttic?
我们得再结一次婚了
We get to get married again!
不 严格意义上讲 我觉得你们已经结了
No,no,technically,I think you guys are still married.
对 但是现在我们能有一个 我梦想中的完美婚礼了
Yeah,but now we get to have the perfect wedding that I always wanted.
- 宝贝 我们的婚礼很完美 - 是啊 对别人来说
- Babe,our wedding was perfect. - Yeah,to everyone but us.
就因为你的拉拉素食姨妈养牛 我们没能吃到烧牛肉
We didn't get the prime rib we wanted because your lesbian vegan aunt adopts cows,
还有你那两岁的侄女 你姐死乞白赖要她做花童
and what about your 2-year-old niece that your sister begged to be our flower girl
而且承诺她会使坐便
and swore was potty-trained?
结果她在红地毯上留下的可不止花瓣
Se petals were not the only thing she dropped in that aisle.
- 没那么糟吧 - 是粑粑 Brad
- It wasn't that bad. - Poops,brad.
Madison在我们的婚礼上拉粑粑 现在我们必须弥补这个缺憾
Madison pooped on our wedding. But now we get to do it right!
这场婚礼一定会很棒的
This is gonna be so great!
- 多谢了 Max - 绝对是Shershow
- Thanks a lot,max. - Classic shershow.
你好呀 威斯康星
Hello,wisconsin.
天 求你别再那么叫了
Oh,my god. Would you stop saying that?
这太棒了
This is so nice.
我还以为Shershow要是结婚 一定是在女子监狱里
I always thought if shersw ever got married,it'd be in a women's prison.
Jane 电话是律师打来的
Jane,that was the lawyer.
说咱们只需很简单的手续 就是名正言顺的夫妻了
All we gotta do is sign some papers,and we're 100% married.
不需要重办婚礼了
No re-wedding necessary.
晚了 婚礼已经在计划中了
Too late. Brain wheels are already turning.
你知道你在说什么吗
You know what that gesture actually means,right?
怎么了 傻佬们
What's up,nerds?
要带着你的杂货铺出行呀 Shershow
Going with the grocery bag luggage thing now,shershow?
这叫绿色低碳生活 好好学学吧，尾气男
Uh,it's called living a green lifestyle. You might wanna look into it,big oil.
等我明天一展神威地主持婚礼的时候
And I'll show you how un-shershow I am
你们就知道 我多不像Shershow了
when I officiate the crap out of his wedding ceremony tomorrow.
- 跟你赌二十块 我会把你感动到哭 - 你根本没有二十块
- I bet you all 20 bucks I make you cry. - You don't have 20 bucks.
我可以拿二十块钱来剔牙的 因为我根本不在乎
I will find 20 bucks and use it as dental floss, 'cause I won't need it so bad,
而且Penny才是受Shershow影响最大的人
and besides,penny is the one that is shershow.
她的备胎要结婚了 多大的打击啊
I mean,her safety's getting married. How depressing is that?
得了吧 Max 我从来就没打算跟那家伙结婚
Okay,come on,max. I was never gonna marry that guy.
跟他结婚...丢脸丢到家了
And anybody who would... Must be busted in la fa-ce.
大家好
Hey,guys!
- 还挺有脸的呀 - 可恶
- More like awesome in la fa-ce? - damn.
真高兴你们能来
I'm so glad that you guys made it.
你看上去真帅 而且...还挺香嘛
You look great! And you... My god,you smell good.
是啊 我学到了铝盐是体香剂的重要原料呢
Yeah,I realized that aluminum is a really important component of deodorant.
各位 都还好吗
Everybody,how are you?
给大家介绍一下我爱人 这是Melinda
Let me introduce you to my love. This is melinda.
通知地这么急 你们还能来 我真高兴
I am so happy that you guys were all able to make it on such short notice.
我下周得出差去洪都拉斯派送太阳能烤箱
I'm leaving next week to deliver solar ovens to honduras.
Shershow 你小子中了头彩啦
Shershow,you hit it out of the park.
她很漂亮 而且她说"洪都拉斯"很好听
She's both biful and says "honduras" the fancy way.
- 她真的很漂亮 - 她简直是个真人版洋娃娃
- She's really pretty. - Pretty? I mean,she's a living doll.
- 我喜欢你 - 注意言辞
- I am attracted to you. - Conduct.
- 非常喜欢 而且我是同性恋 - 好吧
- Very much so,and I am a gay man. - Okay.
是啊 你们能相信我居然娶了 这么好的女孩儿吗
Yeah. Can you believe that I got a girl like this?
Pen 我之前都有点指着咱俩的备胎协议了
Pen,I was kinda counting on our safety pact.
我怕我会跟那些老光棍一样孤独终老
I was afraid I was gonna end up like one of those sad lonelies,you know?
独自在街头落泪的那些
The kind that cry at intersections.
幸好我没那么倒霉
Good thing I dodged that bullet.
你最近怎么样 还好吗
So what's been going on with you? How are you?
- 我订婚了 - 什么
- I'm engaged! - What?
是啊
Yeah.
Penny 那太好了 你订婚了 跟谁啊
So,penny,that's great. You-you got engaged. To who?
跟...我的未婚夫
Uh,my fianc?
他人在哪儿呢 怎么没跟你一起过来
So where's your fianc? Why isn't he here with you now?
路上有暴风雨 常有的事
There is a storm. Storm's a-comin'.
- 从海岸和海峡那边传来 - 很大的暴风雨
- Up the coast and the channels. - Big storm.
所以他实在来不了 不过呢
So he really couldn't make it,but you know what?
怎么又打电话 他很黏我的 整天CALL我 失陪啦
Uh,why are you calling me? He obsessed with me. He calls me constantly. Excuse me.
- 各位 Jason跟我说了很多关于你们的事 - Jason是谁
- Anyways,you guys,jason has told me so much about you. - Who's jason?
那是Shershow的本名 你太像Shershow了 所以不知道
That's shershow's first name. It's so shershow that you don't know that.
Max...Brad...Jane...Dave...Alex
Max... Brad... Jane... Dave... Alex.
抱歉各位 我得离开一下
I'm sorry,you guys. I actually have to get going.
我得去告诉我的姨妈Cathy 这不是她的婚礼
I have to tell my aunt cathy that this isn't her wedding.
同意 我也讨厌催命的亲戚 就好像今天是他们婚礼一样
Yeah,totally. I hate pushy relatives. It's like,"this my day! " right?
不是的 她很久前就得了老年痴呆
No,not right. She has advanced alzheimer's,
对我家来说这真是一个困难时期 她觉得现在是1952年呢
and it's been a really trying time for my family. She thinks it's 1952.
如果她在宾馆见到Brad 肯定歇斯底里了
She's gonna freak out when she sees brad in the hotel.
- 是啊 - 抱歉
- Yeah. - Sorry.
没事
It's okay.
她是不是看我有点不顺眼啊
Did it seem like she was cold to me,or...
她觉得你是婚礼扫把星吧
Yeah,she thinks that you're a wedding jinx,
担心你会毁了这个周末的
so she's really worried that you're gonna ruin the weekend.
神马 婚礼扫把星 我只毁过一个婚礼
What? A wedding jinx? I've only ruined one wedding.
小野洋子也只是毁了一个披头士而已
Yeah,and yoko only ruined one beatles.
我去办入住
I'm gonna check in.
房间 你好啊 希望你准备好有人在你里面嘿咻了
Hello,room. Hope you're ready for some sex to be had in you.
拜托你不要每次入住 都叨唠这句话
Okay,you don't have to say that to every hotel room we stay in.
讲礼貌而已
It's just a courtesy.
Shershow-Rogers的婚礼 10月19日 我喜欢我们纪念日的日期
"shershow-rogers wedding,october 19th. " I love our anniversary date.
神啊
Oh,my god.
如果我们明天结婚 我们的纪念日就没变日期
If we got married tomorrow,we could still have the same anniversary.
但是明天Shershow结婚啊
But tomorrow's shershow's wedding.
所以我们就在他结婚后 反正所有朋友都在
So we'll just do it right after,up here with all our friends.
太棒了 完美
- I mean,it does- - Great. Perfect,perfect.
我要订蛋糕和鲜花
I am gonna order the cake and the flowers
你能不为冒牌婚礼的事抓狂吗
Look,can you please not get too crazy with this whole fake wedding thing?
- 我犯了个大错 - 可不嘛
- I made a big mistake. - Ya think?
我恐慌了 虽然我是个独立的女性
I panicked. I mean,I'm an independent woman and everything,
但是不论你如何去唱Liz Phair的歌
but no matter how hard you sing along to liphair
美国女歌手 自小被遗弃 性格独立
或你去了多少次女性冲浪营
or how many women's surf camps you go to,
到了关键时刻 还是要假装有未婚夫
when the chips are down,you're going fake fianc?
没什么大不了的 就跟Shershow说你未婚夫来不了了
No big deal. Just tell shershow that your fianc? couldn't make it.
可能有点太晚了
It might be too late for that.
最近怎么样啊 骚货们 我又胖了
What's up,skanks?! Whee! I'm fat.
你们还记得Derrick吧
Hey,you guys remember derrick.
你们当然记得我 但是我可不记得你们了
You guys so remember me,and I don't remember you.
开玩笑呢 你是Max Brad和路人金发妞
Just kidding. It's max,brad,and some blonde lady.
Penny 馅饼 真的 我得去补补妆了
Penny pasta,seriously,I need to go to the little girls room.
开来的路上喝了太多 半咖啡因的脱脂拿铁
I've had so many half-caf skim lattes on the drive up,okay?
别迷恋哥 哥只是个传说
This right here - It's happening,okay?
您就等着看好戏吧
Get into it. Drama.
这么点时间里就只能找到他了
He's all I could get last minute.
伙计们 他完全罩的住 他副修的是表演呢
Guys,he can totally pull off straight. In college,he minored in theater.
是啊 他主修的是男人
Yeah,but he majored in dudes.
哇 菇凉 够劲
Whoa,girl. Damn.
你也同意 Melinda有点疯了
Hey,so you agree. Melinda's being crazy.
世界上根本没有婚礼扫把星 对吧
There's no such thing as a wedding jinx,right?
没有 我们的婚礼很顺利啊
No,no,our wedding went off without a hitch.
顺利的没人结成婚 逗你玩的
Literally,nobody got hitched. Kidding!
我们还是朋友 还能一起参加彩排晚宴
We are here,we're friends,and we are gonna do it up at this rehearsal dinner.
也许你会遇到个帅哥 我会遇到个靓女
Hey,maybe you'll meet a guy. Maybe I'll meet a girl.
是啊 最近我在男生公寓里运气不好
Yeah,well,I haven't had much luck in the guy department lately.
等等 我们没准可以互为帮手
Wait. You know,um,maybe we could be each othes wingmen.
我们能那么做吧 我们是铁哥们啊
I mean,we could do that,right? We're buds.
绝对的
Totally. Yeah.
- 那么 你想当我的帮手咯 - 是的
- So... You wanna be my wingman? - I do.
六个月前你干嘛来着
Where was that six months ago?
逗你玩 开玩笑
Kidding! I'm kidding.
给你
Here we go.
Penny 你看起来好漂亮 给我介绍介绍这个幸运的家伙
Hey,penny. You look stunning. So introduce me to the lucky guy.
Shershow 这是Derrick
Shershow,this is derrick.
我的名字 不要到外面乱讲哦
That's my name,so don't wear it out.
肿么了
What's happening?
这开胃小菜...
This hors d'oeuvre is,like...
绝对怪了 对吧
Really weird,right?
是啊 我想也挺怪的
Yeah,I guess it is weird...
婴儿乳蛋饼 像小蛋黄派
Baby quiche. It's like a tiny... Egg pie.
好了 我要去四处转转
Great. Well,uh,i'm gonna go mingle.
喝点热柠檬茶
Have some hot tea with lemon.
拜拜
Bye!
神啊 Penny 我们真的做到了
Oh,my god! Penny,penny ty pennington,we are so doing it!
这周末我要赢个托尼奖
I'm gonna win a tony this weekend.
你装直男 就必须要学火爆浪子里的约翰屈伏塔吗
Really? Your idea of playing straight is danny zuko from "grease"?
你不喜欢 没问题 哥会的东西老了去了
You don't like it. It's not a problem. I've got plenty in the kitty.
欢乐一家亲里的Niles也成 Frasier 你不觉得
Niles from "frasier. " Oh,frasier,don't you think it's-
- 没用的 - 我就会这些了
- That's not gonna work. - That's all I've got.
神啊 救救我吧
Oh,my god.
我可没看到帅气多金男青年
I'm not seeing a very deep talent pool here.
等等 这个人有...牙套
Oh,wait,wait,wait. Now this guy's got some... Braces.
你好啊 目标确认
Hello. Target acquired.
好吧 我这就去
All right,I'm on it.
我擦
Jeez.
娘啊
Oh,god.
- 能请你放着别动吗 - 好吧
- Can you please just leave it? - Yeah.
她就是那个婚礼扫把星
She's the wedding jinx.
- 哇 这些真不错 - 比不上虾好
- Mmm,these are good. - Not as good as shrimp.
虾 我可喜欢虾了 这儿有吗
Shrimp? I love shrimp. There's shrimp here?
这儿没有 跟咱们的婚礼一样
No,no shrimp,just like there wasn't any shrimp at our wedding.
记得吗 都是因为你堂兄Erin会过敏
Remember? 'cause your cousin erin was so allergic.
不过这次一切会有所不同了
But things could be different this time.
咱这次 给你俩字"虾塔"
Two words for you - "shrimp fountain."
答曰"哥好喜欢"
Four words - "i like shrimp fountains."
那是你应得的
Then you shall have one.
我来负责蛋糕 这有家烘培坊 巧克力好吃的让你想哭
And I can get my cake because there's a local bakery that makes a ganache that'll make you cry.
那妞完全忽悠了我
Woman totally played me.
继续 舀吧
Go on. Scoop it up.
对了 忘了告诉你 Dave有自己的餐车
It's true. Oh,I forgot to tell you that.
天哪 你有食物做的车吗
O.m.g. You have a truck made out of food?
请稍等一下
Give us a sec?
- 我们得继续寻找 - 跟她在一起 我觉得自己智商爆棚了
- We need to keep looking. - I've never felt so smart.
你们看到Derrick了吗
Have you guys seen derrick?
他提过跟Kenickie见面 唱蝎子乐队歌曲一较高下
Oh,yeah,he mentioned something about meeting up with kenickie to race the scorpions.
- 那挺好的啊 - 多谢了
- That was good. - Thanks.
- 哎呀 - 那看起来不太妙
- Yikes. - That didn't look good.
我和Mel自十岁起就是闺蜜
Mel and I have been best friends since ere 10.
我愿意一直跟她谈天说地
I would do that again and again.
Jason以后也会成为我的闺蜜 因为你们拜了天地
And now I have two best friends. Love you,melinda and jason.
新郎这边有人要说几句吗
Okay,would anyone from the groom's side like to say anything?
- 不不 - 别去啊 Pen...
- no. No,no,no. - Don't,pen. Pen...
我要来说几句 你很美 不过姐更美
Boop,boop. I want to say something. I do. You're cute,but I'm cuter.
大家好啊
Hey,everybody.
- 姐的芳名是Penny Hartz - 没错
- My name is penny hartz. - yep.
我是Shershow的旧友之一
and I'm one of shershow's oldest friends.
咱俩现在同时坠入爱河了 多好啊
And how amazing is it that we both fell in love at the same time?
你找到了Melinda 我有Derrick
You found melinda,and I... I found derrick.
唱吧 小妞
Sing it,bitch!
诡异之夜
Magical night.
祝福Melinda和Shershow
So congratulations,melinda and shershow.
你们已经找到彼此
You have found each other,
现在你们可以做自己了
and now you will never have to pretend to be something that you're not.
不妙
Not nice.
让我们举杯 姐要翻了
So let's raise our glasses - Going down.
- 绝对的Shershow - 露点了唉
- Classic shershow. - That's a nipple.
今晚Pen真不好过
Oh,rough night for pen.
可怜的娃 她像滑雪橇一样骑那玩意
Oh,poor girl. She rode that thing like a bobsled.
就是
Yeah.
我很想邀你进屋 但Brad对咱的房间保证过 我照他说的做
I'd invite you in,but brad made a promise to our hotel room that I gotta help him keep.
没关系啦 去吧 我自己能行
That's all right. Go on. I'm fine on my own.
哦 天哪
Oh,boy.
- 你好 - 客房服务
- Hello? - Housekeeping?
你能晚点再来吗
Can you... Come back... Later?
人家正要嘿咻一番
I'm about to have sex.
- 好的 - 谢谢
- Yeah. - Gracias.
你昨晚后来怎么样
How'd the rest of your night go?
没怎么样 就睡了
Didn't do much. Just... Went to bed.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Oh,yeah? - Yep.
- Tiffani当时也在床上 我们就做了 - 被发现了吧
- And tiffani was in that bed,and we had sex. - Busted.
你知道我有多喜欢镇得住场的演讲者
Well,you know... How I love great public speakers.
- 你这帮手挺靠谱的 - 多谢夸奖
- And you-you were a fantastic wingman. - Thank yo
咱们这朋友关系真不错
this me-and-you-friends thing is kinda nice.
是挺好的
Yeah,it is nice.
你知道还有啥不错嘛 Tiffani在做的时候...
You know what else was nice? Tiffani was doing this thing -
够了
all right.
跟Max和Brad说吧
Tell max and brad.
然后你夺过麦克风
And then you grabbed the mic
说了15分钟关于两性不同的单口相声
and did 15 minutes of stand-up about the difference between men and women.
至少我没爆料我的韩裔奶奶
At least I didn't bust out my... Korean grandma!
Geisha奶奶 她出柜了
Oh,grandma geisha? She came out.
你们收到咱们无纸化的邀请了吗
Hey,guys,did you get our paperless post invitation?
你是指你们在Shershow婚后 怪异的重婚大典吗 收到了
Oh,you mean to your weird re-wedding after shershow's real wedding? Yeah.
请尽快确定你们的出席情况 我好算人头数
Yeah. Just make sure you r.s.v.p. So I can get an exact head count.
- 我们总共就六个人 - 是啊
- There's only six of us. - Yep.
就关心出席情况 别的甭管 懂吗
Just r.s.v.p. Don't see what the big problem is. Okay?
你至少只会发酒疯
At least you only act crazy when you're drunk.
天哪 Shershow要当逃跑新郎了
Oh,my god. Shershow is runaway grooming it.
那不叫逃跑吧 我看是闲晃
I wouldn't call that running away. He's kinda more sauntering.
他是晃跑新郎
He's the sauntering-away groom.
Shershow 不要去哪儿
Shershow,where are you going?
我想试试 车是否装得下所有的行李
Um,I was just trying to see... If all the luggage fit in the car.
别装了
Oh,nice try.
但你昨晚说的话真的吓到我了
Yeah,but what you said last night really freaked me out.
我是说 我已经不是自己了
I mean,I am-i'm pretending to be meone I'm not.
我不该是这样的 我是Shershow
I'm not this guy. I'm shershow.
但是 你不再是了
But... You're not.
你现在有工作 还有一辆豪华两厢
You've got a job now and a car with a hatchback.
是啊 很酷吧 装卸行李不费吹灰之力
Yeah,it's pretty sweet,huh? It makes loading and unloading a breeze.
但我们都心知肚明 我只会把这一切搞砸
But we both know that i'm just gonna end up screwing all this up.
我会在有重要会议的那天睡过头
I mean,I'm gonna oversleep some morning where we have a really big meeting,
他们会派我去参加一些聚会 而我只会傻乎乎带回来一条蟒蛇
or they're gonna send me out to get a party sub, and I'm just gonna come back with a python.
你为什么这么做
Why would you do that?
因为我是Shershow啊
Because I'm shershow.
我是那种即使没有吃芥末酱 衣服上也会粘到芥末的傻帽
I'm the type of guy who-who gets mustard on his shirt when i'm not even eating mustard.
我是Shershow 我就是这样的
I'm shershow! That's who I am.
你不再是原来的你了 你现在是Jason了
Not anymore you're not. You are jason now.
- 你配得上像Melinda那样的好姑娘 - 真的吗
- And you deserve an amazing girl like melinda. - Really?
当然 快去结婚吧
Yeah. Now let's go get you married.
- 好 - 好...这真沉
- Okay. - Okay. Ooh,that's a heavy one.
- 我来 - 好的
- Okay. - Yeah.
真不敢相信他们让我坐在最后
I can't believe they made me sit back here.
根本没有婚礼扫把星这回事
There's no such thing as a wedding jinx.
这可不妙
That can't be good.
拜托 不要 别走
Oh,come on. Don't go,don't go.
似曾相识的感觉啊
This feels familiar.
我这就去跟Melinda谈谈
I gotta go talk to melinda.
- 你别去 - 我必须去
- No,you don't wanna do that. - I have to.
她还是去了
And she's doing it.
凭我的经验 这不是个好兆头
In my experience... This is not gonna turn out well.
- 真的 - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我要不要去追她
Should I go after her?
追不追都没关系了
It doesn't matter.
那我还是留下吧
I'll stay.
Melinda 听着 别做傻事
Melinda... Look,don't do this.
我知道你一定很害怕
Okay,I know you're scared.
你大概通过那条红毯看见了你的未来
You probably looked down that aisle and saw your whole future,
那并不完美 但是这不代表它不会越来越棒
and it wasn't perfect,but that doesn't mean it can't be great.
不要步我的后尘
Okay,don't do what I did,
否则到最后你只能和你今生的挚爱
or you'll wind up pretending to be best friends
佯装好朋友了
with the guy who could've been the love of your life.
不 我没有要逃跑
No,I wasn't running away.
我的胸罩坏了 整个胸部差点都露出来
My bustier broke,and my boobies were just all over the place.
它们看起来很性感 那我走了
Well... Well,they look hot now. So I'm going to go.
我只是 来看看事情还顺利吗
I just... Wanted to make sure everything was okay.
很好
Yeah,fine.
我要走了
I'll go now.
把这个给我 谢谢
I'm gonna need that. Yeah. Thank you.
"只要在你怀里 我的心就会平静"
"... In your embrace,my heart retreats.
"爱情 能够超越时间"
"love-a force of beating time.
- "爱情 能够彻底让我臣服" - 该死的
- Love-a war I cannot fight... " - damn,man.
贱人
That son of a bitch.
好吧 我输了20块 但是很值得
Well,lost 20 bucks,but it's worth it.
"沉睡不是为了进入梦乡"
"because to sleep is not to dream.
"沉睡是为了不再离开你的怀抱"
" "to sleep is to not leave your touch.
"我宁愿几天几夜与你厮守 不愿睡去"
For a few hours and days,I would rather stay awake.
Jason Melinda 我宣布你们结为夫妻
" Jason,melinda... I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你和Melinda之间进行了很激烈的对话吧
so... Pretty intense convo between you and melinda.
什么 没有 我只是...
What? No. That? I was just...
为了让她回去参加婚礼 口不择言了
I was saying anything I could to get her to come back out to the wedding.
我当时只是给她当头一棒
I mean,I wathis close knocking her over the head
像警察抓小偷似的 把她逮回来
and walking her out like "weekend at bernie's" style.
- 完全正确 我也是这么想的 - 是啊
- Right,totally. That's what I thought. - Yeah.
恭喜你不用再当婚礼扫把星了
Well,congrats on not being the wedding jinx anymore.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 想跳舞吗 - 好啊
- Wanna danc - yeah
你还好吗
You okay?
我不是为了Shershow感伤
Yeah. I'm not-i'm not emotional about shershow.
我是被你的仪式感动了
I'm emotional 'cause of your ceremony.
你太牛逼了 先引用祖父葬礼悼词
It was genius to go neruda
又连着用了Neruda和Sade的诗 真够一气呵成
after sade after quotes from dead grandparents. You nailed it.
Penny 我作为牧师的职责
Penny,my job as the man of the clot
就是在教会与互相尊重的夫妇之间
is to create a bridge between the congregation
建立一座桥梁
and the couple built on honesty and mutual respect.
快把钱给我 混账
Now give me that money,bitch!
怎么了
what's wrong?
你想让我谈谈此时的感受吗
You gonna make me talk aut feelings?
好啊
Fine.
此处省略一百字 你是个好女孩
Blah,blah,blah. You're a great girl.
此处省略一千字 你会遇到个好男人
Blah,blah,blah. You're gonna meet a great guy.
此处省略一万字 现在你至少还有我 来跳舞吧
Blah,blah,blah. Until then,you got me. Let's dance.
你是我的同志备胎
You're my gay-fty- My gay safety.
- 我知道 - 好吧 谢谢
- I got it. - Okay. I wasn't sure. Thanks.
宝贝 我想了想 把蛋糕和虾都退掉了
babe,I thought about it,and I canceled the cake and shrimp and stuff.
我们差一点就能办成完美的婚礼了 你怎么放弃了
We were so close to having a perfect wedding. Why'd you give it up?
你愿意和我一起做这么疯狂的事
The fact that you were willing to go along with me on this insane idea
让我明白了 我不需要完美的婚礼
made me realize I don't need the perfect wedding.
我已经有了完美的丈夫
I have the perfect husband.
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 呸呸 撒酷啦 大金 Achilles之踵 阿吐 校对: 王棫垚 时间轴: 卡灰 双语合成兼压制：神秘人士</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-
<font color=#38B0DE>幸福终点站 第1季 -=第12集
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-</font>